# Karolina Ruda

+48 519 184 982 · karolina1998@vip.onet.pl · https://github.com/KarolinaR98 Szczecin, Poland

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Skilled IT Engineer with 4 years of experience in the game industry. I am currently focused on developing my skills in front-end development. My passion for technology, strong understanding of the visual aspects of applications, and attention to detail, which I honed as a technical artist, allow me to excel in roles that combine design and programming. I am ready for a new career path where I can blend my creativity with technical expertise to deliver modern and intuitive front-end solutions.

#### **KEY COMPETENCIES**

HTML REST API Clean Code
CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, Tailwind WordPress Strategic thinking
RWD MongoDB Problem-solving
JavaScript, TypeScript, C# GIT Fast learner
ReactJS, jQuery, AJAX, Redux Figma, Adobe Photoshop SCRUM

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Game Factory 2021 - 2024

**Technical Artist** 

Worked on the development and optimization of a mobile game with over 10 million users. Paid particular attention to the visual layer and the responsiveness of the application. Recognized for efficiency, reliability, attention to detail, and commitment to improving the project. Successfully streamlined several processes and prepared project documentation.

Game Factory 2020 - 2021 QA Specialist

Identifying, reporting, and tracking bugs to ensure smooth gameplay.

# Educational Foundation "Równe Szanse"

2020

#### **Unity Developer (Internship)**

Developing and implementing game systems using C#, optimizing performance, debugging, and working on game design and logic. Importing assets and maintaining clear technical documentation.

#### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

### **B.S.** in Computer Science

West Pomeranian Business School 2017-2021

Front End Developer Course - Akademia 108

CLA - C Programming Language Certified Associate

# LANGUAGES

Polish - Native English - C1

## **INTRESTS**

Music and piano playing Running Psychology